fbrushes.com 2019-12-30

# FBrushes Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**  

FBrushes does not collect personally identifiable information such as, first and last name, street address and phone number. FBrushes.com does collect email addresses for its own newsletter subscription purposes. These email addresses are never sold or rented to anyone else and are not used for any other purpose.

**IP Addresses**

When you access our website, our website servers register the type of web browsers that you are using and your IP address.An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a Web server when you're on the Web. We collect IP addresses to obtain aggregate information on the use of FBrushes.com. We only use the information we find out from tracking IP addresses in the aggregate, such as how many users entered a specific area of our site, and not to track a specific IP address to identify an individual user. However, we may use such information to identify a user if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security issues or to comply with legal requirements.

**Links**

FBrushes may contain links to other websites. These sites may have separate and independent privacy policies for which FBrushes is not responsible for. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on FBrushes are sometimes served directly to users by third party advertisers. These third party ad services may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Occasionally, as part of advertising programs, third-party advertisers may collect personally identifiable information, such as email address and name, for promotional and advertising activities.

FBrushes does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers 

**Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to this policy**

If we decide to change this policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 12/21/2013

**Contacting Us**  

In case of any questions, please contact us on info(at)FBrushes(dot)com.
